<module>
	<rawname>ivr</rawname>
	<name>IVR</name>
	<version>2.5.20</version>
	<type>setup</type>
	<category>Inbound Call Control</category>
	<description>
		Creates Digital Receptionist (aka Auto-Attendant, aka Interactive Voice Response) menus. These can be used to send callers to different locations (eg, "Press 1 for sales") and/or allow direct-dialing of extension numbers. 
	</description>
	<changelog>
		*2.5.20* Add retvm
		*2.5.19.2* #2987, #3005 sqlite3 install script, spelling
		*2.5.19.1* #2965 not working on IE fixed
		*2.5.19* #2865 Add alternative messages to play if t or i are hit, replacing the first announcmement
		*2.5.18.1* #2948 don't allow deletion if used by a Queue and show list
		*2.5.18* #2066 Migrate recordings to recording ids
		*2.5.17.1* #2845 tabindex
		*2.5.17* #2858 Better handing of i and t options, added loop count and ability to loop before going to user defined i, t options
		*2.5.16.3* #2604, #2843 fix mal-formed html tags, Russian Translation
		*2.5.16.2* #2687 breakout from Queue to Company Directory blocks voicemail
		*2.5.16.1* #2591, added depends on 2.4.0
		*2.5.16* Extension/dest registry, #2303, it translation
		*2.5.15.1* bump for rc1
		*2.5.15* bump version to be higher than 2.2 branch
		*2.5.14.2* merge findmefollow/core extension destinations if any
		*2.5.14.1* removed depends on 2.2.2 - classes are in all version of 2.3
		*2.5.14* add waitexten to 2.2
		*2.5.13.1* make sure t ext getting put in (for some reason it wasn't always, this shoudl fix it)
		*2.5.13* #1871 't' extension not being created by default fixed
		*2.5.12* skip the answer/wait(1) if channel is already answered
		*2.5.11* Allow option for IVR to loop back to itself without corrupting the return-to-ivr to the parent
		*2.5.10* Fix bug where pressing enter in a field would delete the IVR
		*2.5.9* some tweaks because of strange inheritance behavior, so need to reset IVR variables upon returns for some looping conditions
		*2.5.8* insert a return extension so that annoucements and ivrs returning don't trample back over the top
		*2.5.7* extended schema and added ability to have ivr options to return to calling parent ivrs if appropriate, otherwise specified destination
		*2.5.6* Added: Set(IVR_CONTEXT=${CONTEXT}) to facilitate simple returns to calling context (e.g. from an announcement or custom app)
		*2.5.5* Fix bug #1651 and apply patch #1664, allow voicemail as destination if ivr is entered from a queue breakout option
		*2.5.4* Fix bug #1417
		*2.5.3* Add he_IL translation
		*2.5.2* Updated for freepbx 2.2.0rc2
		*2.5.1* Changed name to IVR (from Digital Receptionist)
		*2.5* First release for FreePBX 2.2 - Fixed compatibility issue with new UI
	</changelog>
	<depends>
		<version>2.5.0alpha1</version>
		<module>recordings ge 3.3.8</module>
	</depends>
	<menuitems>
		<ivr>IVR</ivr>
	</menuitems>
	<location>release/2.5/ivr-2.5.19.2.tgz</location>
	<md5sum>58f982062a5e1c28461ad403a30cb712</md5sum>
</module>
